-你肯定是我们中的一员  -谁们
- You must be one of us. - One of who?
灵力者
One of the psychics.
这世上还有其他我们这样的人
I mean, there are others like us out there
我们都是一个大计划的一部分
and we're all a part of something.
(忆往昔)
我们都有灵力
We both have psychic abilities.
萨姆  麦克斯是个坏人
Sam, Max is a monster.
他已经杀了两人  还想杀第三个
He's already killed two people, now he's gunning for a third.
-我觉得我是来帮助你的  -没人能帮我
- I think I'm here to help you. - No one can help me.
这世上有其他像我这样的人
There are people out there, like me.
我们都有一种能力
We all have some kind of ability.
-能力  -对
- Ability? - Yeah.
灵力
Psychic ability.
这些灵力者
These people out there, these psychics,
-他们危险吗  -不都是
- they dangerous? - Not all of them.
但有些是的  有些很危险
But some are. Some are very dangerous.
谁知道这世上究竟有多少
Who knows how many of 'em are really out there?
卡西迪奥
Castiel?
你离开天堂后
After you left heaven,
是什么时候开始觉得
when did it start to feel like...
你融入这里  属于这里
like you fit, like you... belonged here?
你是属于这里的
You do belong here.
我就是需要点时间来跟上时代
it's just gonna take me a second to catch up.
我能照顾好自己
I can handle myself.
你原来很厉害  是吧
You were good at this, weren't you?
非常厉害
Very.
妈妈  你想说什么
Mom... w-what are you trying to say?
我得离开
I have to go.
我需要点时间
I just need a little time.
我爱你们两个
I love you both.
(如今)
(爱荷华州  梅森市)
奥利维亚
Olivia?
[外语]
[邪恶力量 第12季第4集]
(圣经)
瓦迪坎特神父
Father Valdecantos?
我是迪比克总教区的潘恩神父
I'm Father Penn of the Dubuque Archdiocese.
-这位是...  -德尼罗神父
- This is - Father DeNiro.
我们为奥利维亚·桑切斯而来
We're here to talk about Olivia Sanchez.
我不想再谈那事了
I'm not talking about that anymore.
你对媒体和警察可没少说
You sure were chatty with the press and the cops.
"神父声称恶魔行走人间"
"Priest Claims Demons Walk Among Us."
好吸引眼球的标题
Boy, that's quite the headline grabber.
-我说了我不想再谈...  -我们听到了
- I said I'm not talking about - No, we heard you.
不管
Don't care.
你会认为我在撒谎  就像主教  就像所有人
You'll think I'm lying, like my bishop, like everyone.
但我认识奥利维亚
But I knew Olivia.
她是个好人
She was a good person.
我眼看着她被隐形的力量鞭笞至死
I watched her get flayed alive by some invisible force.
那是魔鬼干的
That was the devil's work.
我被告知教会不希望我们再说这种话
I've been told the church doesn't want us talking like that anymore
太过时了
too old fashioned.
但我清楚我看到了什么
But I know what I saw.
你看到黑烟了吗
You see any black smoke?
-什么  -我们不认为你撒谎了
- What? - We don't think you're lying.
我们只是想问你几个问题而已
We just wanna ask you a few questions, that's all.
没有  没有黑烟
No. No smoke.
硫磺呢  闻到臭鸡蛋味儿了吗
What about sulfur? Did you smell, uh, rotten eggs?
没有
No.
你说她说了外语
You told people that she was speaking in tongues?
是啊  听上去像希伯来语
Yes. It sounded like Hebrew.
[外语]
更像阿拉姆语  而不是希伯来语
Sounds more like Aramaic than Hebrew.
你们是哪门子神父啊
What kind of priests are you?
过时的那种
The old-fashioned kind.
谢谢
Thanks.
没有硫磺就不是恶魔
So no sulfur means no demon.
你觉得神父是对的吗  真是路西法干的
You think the padre's right? We talking about Lucifer here?
这太小儿科了吧
Little small-time for him.
或许是暴走天使
I don't know. Maybe a rogue angel?
迪恩
Dean.
嗯  我去打电话
Yeah. Uh, I'll make a call.
等等  什么  你认真的吗
Wait, wait, wait. What? Are you serious?
是啊  小卡  这很怪  非常怪
Yes, Cass, that's weird. It's really, really weird.
好吧
All right, yeah.
多谢提醒
Thanks for the heads up.
(妈妈  就是问问你还好吗  我还能叫你"妈妈"吗  还是该叫你玛丽)
我成13岁小女生了
Now I'm a 13-year-old girl.
怎么样
So what's the word?
小卡知道什么吗
Cass have anything?
嗯
Yeah.
好消息
Well, good news, uh,
天使电台上没消息  天堂还在封锁中
there's nothing on angel radio, and Heaven's still on lockdown,
所以排除暴走天使
so rogue angel is out.
坏消息呢
Bad news?
小卡跟克劳力搭伙了
Cass is chumming it up with Crowley.
他们在一起追踪路西法
They're hunting Lucifer together.
是啊  一个天使  一个恶魔
That's right -- one's an angel, one's a demon,
还一起破案
and apparently, they solve crimes.
-他们有进展吗  -算有吧
- Are they having any luck? - Kind of.
路西法  邪恶之王  光明天使
So Lucifer, the Lord of Evil, Angel of Light,
现在是烂摇滚大师
is now the Master of Butt Rock.
他跳进了文斯·文森特的身体
He jumped into Vince Vincente.
-那个摇滚明星  -混蛋差不多
- The rock star? - The douchebag.
他以前留长紫发及腚
Guy used to roll with purple hair down to his butt
还穿带尖刺的护挡
and a spiked codpiece.
那是80年代嘛
It -- it was the '80s.
什么
The what?
那是80年代嘛
It was the '80s.
-你还替他说话  -不是
- What, are you defending him? - No, I'm not...
他第三张专辑还挺...
I mean, his third album was kind of...
-不那么差劲  -我现在恨死你了
- not horrible. - I hate you so much right now.
总之  他现在是魔鬼了
Anyway, he's the Devil now?
他一直都算是个魔鬼
Well, I mean, he was always kind of the Devil,
但没错  现在是真正的了
but, yeah, now it's official.
他人呢
Where is he?
罗威娜把他炸到海底了
Rowena blasted him to the bottom of the ocean.
-为什么  -我不知道
- Why? - I don't know.
你为什么会喜欢文斯·文森特
Why do you love Vince Vincente?
我才不喜欢...
I don't love --
总之  我查了那句话
Anyways, uh, looked at those words.
我说对了  是阿拉姆语
I was right. They are Aramaic.
[阿拉姆语]
意思是  "救我  上帝"
It means, "Save me, oh, God."
为什么呼救
Save me from what?
尸体就在这里  探员
Body's right there, Agents.
-我可以做下准备  -太好了  卡尔
- I can get her prepped to your - That's great, Carl.
接下来就交给我们吧
We'll take it from here.
好吧
Okay.
但...这案子挺怪的
But...it's a weird'un.
如果你们有任何需要
If you guys need anything at all,
-我...  -不必  谢谢
- I'm - We won't. We won't. Thank you.
-真的吗  -嗯
- Are...you sure? - Yep.
那好吧
Okay.
对卡尔太粗暴了点吧
Little, uh, tough on Carl, don't you think?
他不小了  能受得了
He's a big boy. He can take it.
你没事吧
You okay?
-好极了  -真的
- Peachy. - You sure?
自从妈妈离开  你一直有点...
'Cause ever since Mom left, you've been a little,
暴躁
cranky.
-暴躁  是吗  -嗯
- Cranky, huh? - Yeah.
对神父  对卡尔
I mean, to the priest, to Carl.
来这儿的路上  你都不肯停车让我解手
Heck, on the way here, you wouldn't even make a pit stop.
你膀胱小还成我的问题了
So now your tiny bladder is my problem?
-我就是想说  -奥利维亚·桑切斯
- I'm just saying - Olivia Sanchez.
尸体发现时
The body was found.
背后有很深的割痕  就像被鞭打过
It had deep cuts on her back as though she'd been whipped.
手脚穿孔
Holes punctured through her hands and her feet,
颅骨顶部有针刺伤
and pinprick wounds around the top of her skull.
你觉得听起来像什么
What's that sound like to you?
圣痕
Stigmata.
是啊
Bingo.
-还有更怪的  -怎么说
- Gets weirder. - How?
"被害人颅骨内满是滑稠状物"
"The victim's skull was filled with a goopy mush."
卡尔文笔真不错  是吧
That Carl paints quite a picture, doesn't he?
好吧
All right.
什么东西有这本事
What can do all that?
我想不到
I got nothing.
我也是
Me neither.
或许我们该把精力多放在案子上
Well, maybe we should focus more on the case
而不是心理治疗
and less on the Dr. Phil crap.
(奥利维亚·桑切斯)
就在这边
It's just over here.
这是...之前是奥利维亚的办公室
This is -- was Olivia's office.
现在呢
So...what is it now?
是我的了
It's...kinda mine now.
这是你的吗
So is that yours?
是为了提供正能量
It's for positive energy.
我是个巫士
I'm a Wiccan.
酷啊
Cool.
你对奥利维亚有多了解
So how well did you know Olivia?
她是我上司
She was my boss.
他们说的是真的吗
Is it true what they're saying,
她...
that she, you know...
是自杀的
killed herself?
我们还在查
Well, we're working on that.
奥利维亚死的那天  有什么异常举动吗
Now the day she died, was Olivia acting strange?
没有
Not really. I mean...
她说头疼  很严重  很厉害的偏头疼
She was getting headaches. Bad ones, like super migraines.
但我们都知道她是工作狂
But we all knew she was working too hard.
她有敌人吗
She have any enemies?
有人对她有宿怨  或许想伤害她的
Somebody who held a grudge, maybe wanted to do her harm?
有
Yeah.
奥利维亚是个大好人
I mean, Olivia was great,
但这里毕竟是儿童保护服务处
but this is Child Protective Services.
我们经常收到威胁
We get threats all the time.
-来自什么人  -各种人
- From who? - Everyone.
有时候  拆散一个家庭才是上策
You don't make a lot of friends when sometimes
所以我们经常得罪人
what's best for a family is to split them up.
是啊
Right.
可以给我们看看奥利维亚的案卷吗
Yeah, can we see Olivia's case files?
当然  就在这边
Of course. They're right over here.
(儿童保护服务处)
-真轻松  -什么
- Well, that was easy. - What?
什么  当然是里面那位西方邪恶女巫
What? The Wicca'd Witch of the West in there.
正能量小姐想要更大的办公室
Little Miss Positive Energy wanted a bigger office,
就施了魔法
did a little hoodoo...
我们干掉这个女巫  就收工吧
I say we put a witch-killing cap in her ass, call it a day.
是啊  但我们查过教堂和奥利维亚家
Yeah, but we checked the church and Olivia's house.
并没有找到巫术袋
We didn't exactly find any hex bags.
那么说她掩盖了证据
So she covered her tracks.
但我们找的不是女巫
But we're not looking at a witch.
我并不是说不是贝丝
I'm not saying it's not Beth.
我是说  我们需要证据
I'm -- I'm just saying we need proof.
如果是她  我亲自打死她
And look, if it's her, I'll shoot her myself.
不不
Oh, no, no, no, no.
绝对要我来打死她
No, I'm definitely shooting her.
救我  上帝
Prok yaw-thi a-law-haw!
验尸官说有圣痕
Coroner says signs of stigmata
外加脑子被搅成浆  跟奥利维亚一样
with a side of scrambled brains, just like Olivia.
-这可好  -有发现吗
- Great. - Did you find anything?
或许吧  他到处送杂货
Maybe. Kid delivered groceries all over town,
我拿他的送货路线跟奥利维亚的案卷做了对比
so I checked his route against Olivia's case files.
-怎么样  -有结果
- And? - Got a match.
跟我们说说彼得森一家
Tell us about the Petersons.
他们很怪
They're weird.
-怎么怪  -非常怪
- How weird? - All the way.
那家人虔诚得爆表
That family, they're, like, off the charts religious.
很信《旧约》
Old, old Testament.
不开车  不用电  什么都不用
I'm talking no cars, no electricity, no nothing.
孩子都在家自学
Kids are homeschooled.
那种家庭  我们都尽量留意  但是
Family like that, we try to keep an eye on them, but...
但是怎么了  贝丝
But what, Beth?
他们的长女  玛格达
Their oldest, Magda --
几年前  她患了肺炎
a few years ago, she got pneumonia,
他们家的人不许医生给她治疗
and the family wouldn't let a doctor treat her.
他们说不管发生什么都是上帝的旨意
They said whatever happened was God's will.
发生了什么
What happened?
她死了
She died.
好吧  谢谢
All right. Um, thank you.
怎么样
So?
古怪  吓人  与世隔绝
Weird, creepy, off the grid,
《玉米田的小孩》式的一家
Children of the Corn people.
我愿去查查
Yeah, I'm in.
(不得擅闯)
看来后面得徒步了
Guess we're walking from here.
他们隔绝电力做得很彻底啊
When they cut the cord, they really cut the cord.
可不是
Yeah, no kidding.
你觉得他们的马车最快能跑多快
How fast you think their buggy goes? Like, top speed?
昨天的事
Hey, about yesterday...
好吧
Oh, all right.
下次你想撒尿  我停车就是了
Next time you gotta take a leak, I'll pull over.
我不是想说那个  我是想说你和妈妈
I'm not talking about that. I'm talking about you and Mom.
她怎么了  她拿了点现金
What about her? What, she took some cash,
她拿走了手机  却不接
she took a cellphone she doesn't answer,
然后抛下我们跑路了
and she bailed on us.
想想她现在的经历
I mean, think about what she's going through.
发生了那么多  她大概只是需要点空间
After everything, she probably just needs some space.
我们也经历过
We've been there.
我们都曾有需要分开的时候
We've both had times where we needed time apart.
-我们都回来了  -你觉得她不会吗
- And we both came back. - You don't think she's going to?
我不知道
I don't know.
她不喜欢我们长大的方式
She hates the way that we were raised.
她不喜欢我们成了猎人
She hates the fact that we're hunters.
或许她一走就不会停下了
Maybe she starts walking and she doesn't stop.
她显然完全不想
You know, she obviously has zero interest
让我们一家人在一起
in keeping this family together.
有时候分开一阵
Well, you know, sometimes families do better
对一个家庭更好
after a little time apart.
哪个家庭  曼森家族吗
Yeah, who? The Mansons?
有事吗
Can I help you?
亚伯拉罕·彼得森吗  我是詹姆斯·莫里森
Abraham Peterson? I'm James Morrison.
这位是我同事  雷·曼扎莱克
This is my associate Ray Manzarek.
我们是儿童保护服务处新派来的你们的案件专员
We're your new case workers with Child Protective Services.
-幸会  -幸会
- Pleasure to meet you. - Pleasure to meet you.
我以为你会是...
Yeah, thought you'd be, uh, you know,
大胡子  吊带裤  大帽子呢
long beard, suspenders, big hat.
我们不是那种信徒
We're not that kind of religious.
彼得森先生和太太
Mr. and Mrs. Peterson,
我们来是因为你们之前的案件专员
we're here because your previous case worker,
奥利维亚·桑切斯
Olivia Sanchez,
已经去世了
has passed away.
怎么回事
What happened?
我们还不确定
We're not sure yet.
她多久来一次
How often did she visit?
每隔几个月
Every few months.
我们喜欢她  比另一个强
We liked her better than the other one --
贝丝
that Beth.
贝丝有什么不好
And what was wrong with Beth?
她因为我们的信仰而讨厌我们
She hated us because of our faith.
奥利维亚·桑切斯是天主教徒
Olivia Sanchez was a Papist, but...
但她至少信奉上帝
at least she believed in God.
你们了解上帝吗  先生们
Do you know God, gentlemen?
是啊
Oh, yeah.
我们...是好哥们
Yeah, we're -- we're besties.
好吧
Okay.
我有点不好意思
I'm a little embarrassed to ask,
但你们中谁能帮我个忙吗
but do you think one of you boys might help me with something?
这种东西坏掉
So what happens when,
又没人来帮你们  你们要怎么办
stuff like this goes wrong and no one's around to help you?
更努力地祈祷
Pray harder.
我不太擅长这些
See, I'm not good with all this.
直到五年前  我还是个计算机程序员
I was a computer programmer till about five years ago.
那你为什么搬到了这种荒郊野岭
What made you move out to the middle of nowhere?
外面的世界都是纷扰
The world out there is all distractions.
消费主义  大企业
Consumerism, corporations.
世人  如果不在购物  或大吃
And the people, if they're not shopping or stuffing their face,
就是坐在一个屏幕前
they're sitting in front of some screen
看着假人作假
watching fake people do fake things,
而真实的世界只是越来越糟
while the real world just gets more and more screwed up.
盖尔和我  不希望孩子变成那样
Gail and I, we didn't want that for our kids, so...
所以我们成了这样  忙得满头大汗
so here we are, sweatin' our butts off.
你为家庭付出的一切啊
The things you do for family.
好了
It's ready.
那好  我们把轮子装上吧
All right, let's get this wheel on.
数到三
On three.
一二三
One, two, three.
好了
Okay.
我们没有咖啡了  希望你喜欢柠檬水
We're out of coffee. Hope lemonade's all right.
-嗯  当然  谢谢你  -不客气
- Oh, yeah. Great. Thank you. - Welcome.
-幸福的一家  -不是的
- Happy family. - No, they weren't.
照片里的父亲一周工作80小时
The father was working 80 hours a week
也只能勉强偿还按揭
to barely pay the mortgage.
他能在家里待的少的可怜的时间里
And what little time he did spend at home,
也都用来喝酒了
he spent in a bottle.
孩子们吃着四种
Children were on four different kinds
能力增强药物  几乎从不说话
of behavior-enhancing medication and barely spoke.
但很会发短信
Could text up a storm, though.
母亲最糟了
And the mother, she was the worst.
她药吃的太多  脑子都不清楚了
She was so pilled up, she could barely think straight.
后来呢
So what happened?
上帝让他们知道有更好的道路
God showed them a better way.
我出了车祸
I was in a car accident.
差点死了
Almost died.
我身体下部的神经受损
Nerves in the lower half of my body are damaged.
我去看了医生
I saw doctors.
没人能减缓疼痛
No one could stop the pain.
他们最多只能给我药物
Best they could do was give me drugs,
-一段时间内是有帮助  -嗯
- which helped for a while. - Yeah.
但我吃得越多  就想吃越多
But the more I took, the more I needed.
我拿不到时...
And when I didn't get them...
然后有一晚
And then one night,
情况跌落谷底  我...
when things were at their worst, I was...
躺在自己的呕吐物里
lying in a puddle of my own sick.
听到了一个声音
I heard a voice.
上帝的声音
It was God's voice.
他说  "去过简单谦卑的生活吧
And he said, "Go, live a life of simplicity and humility,
你的痛苦都将消失"
and all your pain will be taken away."
疼痛消失了吗
So has the pain gone away?
有他的恩典  我能撑过去
I get by, with His grace.
彼得森太太
Mrs. Peterson,
能跟我说说瑞奇·考佩兰吗
what can you tell me about Ricky Copeland?
送货员
The delivery boy?
对
Yeah.
一周来一次
Comes by once a week,
给我们送我们不能自己种的东西
brings us things we can't grow ourselves.
怎么了
Why?
他
Well...
他也死了
He's dead, too.
我知道了
I see.
你知道了
You see?
就这样吗
That's it?
上帝对我们每个人都有安排
God has a plan for us all.
那你女儿的事  也是上帝的安排吗
So what happened to your daughter, was that God's plan?
对
Yes.
她并不非得死的
She didn't have to die.
她病了
She was sick.
如果你肯带她去见医生
If you had taken her to a doctor --
-上帝...  -上帝才不管你过什么样的生活
- God does - God doesn't care what kind of life you live.
相信我
Trust me.
上帝也没杀死你女儿  是你害死了她
And God didn't kill your daughter. You did.
你们该走了
Think you boys should go.
好了  我们清楚该做什么了吧
All right. We're clear on what we gotta do, right?
-是啊  -那是干吗的
- Yeah, definitely. - What's that for?
找玛格达的鬼魂  你...
To track down Magda's ghost. What's...
贝丝  那女巫
Beth. The witch.
-迪恩  这不是女巫干的  -也不是鬼
- Dean, this isn't a witch. - Well, it's not a ghost.
他们任由自己的女儿死去
Those people let their daughter die.
-她很生气  想复仇  -但他们还活着
- She's angry and wants revenge. - Yeah, but they're alive.
而且  她怎么到处跑的
Besides, how -- how she getting around town, huh?
鬼魂是被束缚在一个地方的
Ghosts are tied to one place.
或是束缚在一个人  或一件物上
Or -- or to a person or to a thing.
-你太牵强了  -你就不吗
- Oh, you're reaching. - And you're not?
贝丝都不认识那个送货员
Beth didn't even know the delivery boy.
或许吧  我会去查个明白
Maybe, maybe not, but I'm gonna find out.
你没跟那女人单独接触过
Look, you didn't spend alone time with that woman.
她不正常
She is disturbed.
这家人是挺怪  但他们是好人
The family's weird, but they're good people.
贝丝想要更好的工作  就为此杀人
Look, Beth wanted the better job, she killed to get it.
-就是这样  -你错了
- End of story. - You're wrong.
好吧  你有你的看法  我有我的
All right, look, you got your ideas, I got mine.
你想留下  扫描农场里有没有电磁场
You wanna stay here and, uh, scan the farm for EMF,
你自便  我去查贝丝
you go right ahead. I'm on Beth.
-好啊  看看谁是对的  -肯定我是对的
- Fine. We'll see who's right. - Well, you'll see I'm right.
∮ 我如此欢愉 ∮
∮ I've got the joy, joy, joy, joy. ∮
∮ 心中充满欢乐 ∮
∮ Down in my heart. ∮
∮ 在哪里 ∮
∮ Where? ∮
∮ 就在我心里 ∮
∮ Down in my heart to stay. ∮
∮ 若是魔鬼不喜欢 ∮
∮ And if the Devil doesn't like it. ∮
∮ 让他去坐在钉子上吧 ∮
∮ He can sit on a tack. ∮
∮ 疼啊 ∮
∮ Ouch. ∮
∮ 坐在钉子上 ∮
∮ Sit on a tack. ∮
∮ 疼啊 ∮
∮ Ouch. ∮
∮ 我好开心 ∮
∮ And I'm so happy. ∮
∮ 非常开心 ∮
∮ So very happy. ∮
你做了什么
What did you do?
没什么  没什么
Nothing. Nothing.
撒谎
Liar.
那女人  那男孩
That woman. That boy.
你杀了他们
You killed them.
什么  没有
What? No.
我一直努力把魔鬼锁起来
I have tried to keep the Devil locked away,
你还是放他出来了
and you let him out.
你就是不能不惹事
You couldn't let it rest.
现在
And now...
魔鬼在通过你作恶了
Now the Devil is doing his work through you.
坦白罪孽
Confess your sins.
祈求宽恕
Pray for forgiveness.
救我  上帝
Prok yaw-thi a-law-haw
[阿拉姆语]
以利亚
Elijah?
-怎么了  -妈妈在玛格达那儿
- What's wrong? ‭- Mom's with Magda.
你妈妈在按上帝的旨意行事
Your mother's doing God's work.
她在伤害她
She's hurting her.
儿子  魔鬼会骗人
Son, the Devil's a deceiver.
别让他在你心中洒下怀疑的种子
Don't let him sow doubt in you.
如果有人得知玛格达的事  会来抓她的
If anyone found out about Magda, they'd come for her.
如果发生那种事
And if that happened...
我爱你姐姐
I love your sister...
但你知道她的本事
but you know what she can do.
玛格达
Magda...
玛格达是我们的负担
Magda's our cross to bear.
(无信号)
拜托
Come on.
加班呢
Working late?
抱歉  探员  你吓我一跳
Sorry, Agent, you surprised me.
没事
No worries.
有事吗
Can I help you?
喜欢新工作吗
How you liking the new gig?
很不喜欢
I hate it.
-什么  -是啊
- What? - ‭Yeah.
挣得更多  但活儿也更多
You make more, but you work more.
要是有人搞砸  都要怪到你头上
And if somebody screws up, that's on you.
有人超了截止日期  怪你
If somebody blows a deadline, that's on you.
有人在休息室里复印屁股
And if somebody's photocopying their ass in the breakroom,
你得像个大人一样发火
you have to adult and act all mad,
虽然那样很好笑
even though it's kind of hilarious.
做老板很讨厌的
Being the boss sucks.
真不知奥利维亚怎么做到的
I don't know how Olivia did it.
我以为你想要这份工作呢
I-I thought you wanted this job.
才不  没人想要这份工作
No. Nobody wants this job.
你来有什么事
So...why are you here?
[阿拉姆语]
再来
Again.
Again!
[阿拉姆语]
贝丝不是女巫
Beth is not a witch.
你的鬼魂理论是对的
You were right about the whole ghost thing.
听着  玛格达还活着
Listen, Magda is still alive.
-等等  什么  -是啊  玛格达没死
- Wait, what? - Yes, Magda's not dead.
她还活着
She's alive!
萨姆
Sam.
别动
Don't move.
-萨姆  -听我说
- Sammy? - ‭Okay, listen to me.
我可以帮你姐姐
I can help your sister, okay?
你得相信我
I just need you to trust me here.
萨姆
Sam?
Sammy?
∮ 约书亚打了杰里科之役 ∮
∮ Joshua fought the battle of Jericho. ∮
∮ 城墙都轰然崩塌 ∮
∮ And the walls came tumbling down. ∮
∮ 你可以说你的犹太勇士 ∮
∮ You may talk about your men of Gideon. ∮
∮ 你可以说... ∮
∮ You may talk about your men of... ∮
玛格达
‭Magda?
玛格达·彼得森
Magda Peterson.
那不是我的名字
That's not my name.
我不是玛格达
I'm not Magda.
我是魔鬼
I'm the Devil.
不
No.
不  你不是  你真不是
No, you're not. You're really not.
他在我体内  我听得到他的低语
He's inside me. I can hear him whispering.
他让我听到其他人的想法
He lets me hear what people are thinking.
他让我做事情
He lets me do things.
什么样的事情
What kind of things?
玛格达  我是来帮你的
Magda, I'm here... I'm here to help you.
让我看看
Show me.
求你
Please.
(迪恩)
他们会来抓我们的  我们的孩子
They'll come for us, our children.
我们今晚就得走
We need to leave tonight.
玛格达
Magda...
你不是魔鬼  你只是有灵力
You're not the Devil. You're just psychic.
还有其他你这样的人  我这样的人
There are others out there like you, like -- like me.
我也有灵力
I have powers, too.
我有时会看到幻象
I'd get these visions sometimes
我可以靠念力移动物体
and -- and I could move things with my mind.
你可以吗
You can do that?
现在应该不行了
Well, no, not anymore, I don't think.
但那不代表我是魔鬼
But that didn't make me the Devil.
那只是我的一部分
It -- it -- it just made me who I am.
那你是邪恶的
Then you are evil.
母亲说我是邪恶的
Mother says I'm evil,
因为我伤害人
'cause I hurt people.
你伤了谁
Who did you hurt?
我不是有意的
I didn't mean it.
她那么漂亮
She was pretty,
还总是笑
and she always smiled.
我以为她可以帮我
And I thought that maybe she could help me.
我不能跟她说话  但我听得到她的想法
I couldn't talk to her, but I could hear her thoughts.
我想  或许我可以让她听到我的想法
And I thought maybe I could make her hear mine.
所以我祈祷
So I prayed.
救我  上帝
Prok yaw-thi a-law-haw.
[阿拉姆语]
我向她求助
And I reached out to her...
[阿拉姆语]
但她再没来
But she never came.
然后我又对送货员那么做了
And I did it again with the delivery boy.
母亲说我杀了他们
Mother says I killed them.
玛格达  那不怪你
Magda, that wasn't your fault.
你不是魔鬼  你不邪恶
You are not the Devil. You're not evil.
这很吓人  我知道
And it's scary. I-I know it's scary.
但你可以学会控制它
But you can learn how to control it.
你再也不用伤害任何人了
You don't ever have to hurt anyone ever again.
该吃晚饭了
It's time for supper.
谁饿了
Who's hungry?
亚伯拉罕
Abraham...
你女儿需要帮助
your daughter needs help.
你以为我们这些年都在做什么
What do you think we've been doing all these years?
你说你了解上帝  但我们了解魔鬼
You talk about knowing God, but we know the Devil.
我们跟她纠缠好多年了
We've been wrestling with her for years.
你知道她做了什么吗
You have any idea what she's done?
那些人
Those people, but...
那不能怪她
That wasn't her fault.
你以为他们是最先遭殃的
You think they're the first?
告诉他
Tell him.
我们来到这儿之前
Before we came here...
我想要部新电话
I wanted a new cellphone,
但妈妈不肯给我买
but my mom wouldn't buy me one.
我们当时正开车回家  她大叫着让我停车
We were driving home, and she screamed at me to pull over.
我感到魔鬼握住了我的手
And I felt the Devil at my hands.
我一打轮  冲向了迎面来的车
I yanked that wheel right into oncoming traffic.
是她害我的
She did this to me.
是她害了我们
She did this to us.
她夺走了生命
She has taken lives.
你难道不明白  我们把她关在这儿
Don't you understand that by keeping her here,
是在保护你们
we're protecting you?
做什么  把她打得半死吗
By doing what? Beating the hell out of her?
疼痛能清除罪孽
Pain purges sin.
才不能  你错了
No, it doesn't. You're wrong.
亚伯拉罕
Abraham.
是时候了
It's time.
感谢您赠予的美味食物
We thank you for these bountiful gifts.
愿它们滋养我们的身体和灵魂
May they nourish our body and soul.
请照顾我们每个人
And look after each one of us,
直到我们大限到来
now and until our dying day.
-阿门  -阿门
- Amen. - Amen.
吃吧  各位
Dig in, everyone.
以利亚
Elijah.
爸爸
Dad? ‭
亚伯拉罕
Abraham?
爸爸
Dad?
你做了什么
What did you do?
(老鼠药)
吃啊
Eat.
你做了什么
What did you do?!
我们这样才能永远在一起
This is how we will stay together.
我们将作为一家人进入天堂
We will enter Heaven as a family.
吃啊
Eat!
以利亚  别吃
Elijah, do not eat that.
以利亚
Elijah!
-妈妈  -吃
- Mom? - ‭Eat.
以利亚  别
Elijah, do not do it.
吃啊
Eat!
不要
No! ‭
魔鬼
Devil.
不要
No!
我不是魔鬼  你才是
I'm not the Devil. You are.
玛格达  住手  你不用这么做的
Magda, stop! You don't have to do this.
你可以控制它
You could control it.
玛格达  再不需要死人了
Magda, nobody else has to die. ‭
求你
Please!
她是魔鬼
She's the Devil!
魔鬼就在人间
The Devil is among us!
她必须被净化
She must be cleansed!
她是魔鬼
She is the Devil!
为我们祈祷
Pray for us!
抱歉我错过了疯子发作
Sorry I missed all the psycho.
你还觉得我们家就够疯了
Hey, you thought our family was crazy.
是啊
‭Yeah.
玛格达
Hey, Magda.
你还好吗
Are you holding up?
贝丝给我在加州的姑妈打了电话
Beth called my aunt in California.
我会去跟她住
I'm gonna be staying with her.
她有间农场
She has a ranch.
很开阔的乡村空间
Lots of wide open country.
太好了
Well, that's great.
有时候  人想理清楚思路
You know, sometimes in order to figure things out,
就需要点空间
a person needs space.
探员  能跟你谈谈吗
Agent, can I talk to you?
当然
Yeah, sure.
玛格达  我知道你现在不这么觉得
Magda, I-I know it doesn't feel like it right now,but...
但你不会有事的
you're gonna be all right.
你可以的  你能行的
You can do this. You will do this.
记住
Just remember,
那能力
that power...
它不能控制你
it doesn't control you.
是你控制它
You control it.
我知道
I know.
如果你今后需要什么
If you ever need anything, anything,
都可以打给我
call me, okay?
我会去的
I'll be there.
你觉得你的决定是正确的吗  放了她
Think you made the right call back there, letting her go?
希望是
I hope so. I mean...
玛格达不知道自己做了什么  完全不懂
Magda didn't know what she was doing. She had no idea.
我觉得该给她个第二次机会
I think she deserves a second chance.
贝丝什么事
What did Beth want?
她给了我她的电话  私人电话
She gave me her number, her personal number.
-你本打算杀了她呢  -是啊
- You were gonna shoot her. - Yeah, I know.
挺奇怪的  挺性感的
Kinda weird. Kinda hot.
你刚刚的话是真心的吗
Did you mean what you said back there?
是啊  你说得对
Yeah, you were right.
妈妈的事
This whole mom thing, it's...
她回来了  却又走了
I mean, we get her back, and then she leaves.
我很不爽  但我能理解
I hate it, but I get it. I do.
我大概...就是还在消化这件事
I guess I just...still working through some of that crap.
我会尽量不那么犯浑
I'll try to be less of a dick about it.
好啊
Deal.
(迪恩  电话没电了  又没带充电器  我没事  我永远是"妈妈"  告诉萨姆我爱你们)
-怎么了  -没事
- What? - ‭Nothing.
(圣克鲁兹)
往右去洗手间
All right, bathrooms to the right.
汽水机在左边
Soda machines to the left.
给你们20分钟  然后我们就去加州了
You have 20 minutes, folks. Then we're off to Cali.
怎么样了
What's your status?
我收拾了温家兄弟留下的麻烦
I cleaned up the Winchester's mess.
我们猜中了  他们没能完成任务
As suspected, they couldn't finish the job.
很好  谢谢你  凯奇先生
Very well. Thank you, Mr. Ketch.